Welcome to ZK Dungeon, a decentralized rogue-lite experience built for the DoraHacks Stellar ZK Gaming track.
This demo showcases our single-player MVP in Hackathon Mode, running entirely on the Stellar Testnet.
We begin by connecting our Freighter wallet in testnet mode. In this solo instance, the player goes up against the house.
Connecting the wallet initiates our game session and prepares the on-chain state to track our progress.
Instead of relying on a centralized server to validate moves, ZK Dungeon targets verifiable zero-knowledge gaming.
When a player makes a choice, a zero-knowledge proof is generated locally on the client.
This ensures the player's moves are valid without revealing the dungeon's underlying cryptographic secrets.
Once generated, this proof is submitted to the Stellar Testnet via the connected Freighter wallet.
A Stellar smart contract then verifies the proof on-chain, acting as an impartial, decentralized referee.
This combination of off-chain ZK execution and on-chain verification guarantees a provably fair game.
When the run concludes, the game settles the outcome cryptographically.
True 2-player state channels are actively in progress, but the core ZK verification loop is firmly in place today.
Thank you for watching, and good luck to all teams in the Stellar ZK Gaming hackathon.